Explain how you allowed her to go without you.
If you cannot handle her, you have no purpose.
She is your raison d'être.
If you lose her, your raison d'être is stripped away.
That is the pact between an Entourage and its master.
Iggy, I'm going to immigrant sectors H and J.
Send the car over.
Wait.
Sectors H and J are outside our jurisdiction.
Outside our jurisdiction or not, I have to go.
If you don't want to hear my
grandfather complain, I'll go by myself.
Explain how you allowed her to go without you.
If you cannot handle her, you have no purpose.
You wouldn't understand.
She is your raison d'être.
If you lose her, your raison d'être is stripped away.
That is the pact between an Entourage and its master.
You complete my fate
The world unwinds inside of me
The halo crawls away
You refill my place
Come and save me
Believe in me and drink the wine and take my hand and fill me up
Golo presents
Come and save me
That ship can't navigate through just a little bit of wind like this?
I thought it looked old, but it must be a real piece of junk.
Hey, you.
It seems like I've hurt my leg too.
Do a medical check.
"Medical"...?
Um...
She is a companion-type, so I don't
think she has that kind of function...
So it's not just the ship, but the autoreiv is useless as well.
I'm surprised you could travel this far with them.
Oh,
it must be because you're a PROXY.
Miss Re-l...
Even though you're a PROXY, you
don't even know what PROXIES are.
How ridiculous.
Dammit...
When is it going to stop snowing?
meditation  conceptual blind spot
PROXY...
If only such things didn't exist...
Vincent Law...
That autoreiv is...
Did she come to get the body back?
What?
What have you done?
You!
Take it.
It's just in the way, after all.
Wait.
Was it your master?
Were you looking after that PROXY?
This is...
It's the same.
I see.
These are all-
Did that make these?
What are PROXIES?
No, that doesn't matter.
What's important to me right now is...
What are you going to do?
You've lost your master...
Did you think you could steal the
gun from me while I was sleeping?
No, um... I thought you might catch cold.
Do my hair.
You can do that much, can't you?
Can't you hear me?
I'm reading a book.
What's your problem?
Then you'll do.
Do my hair.
Um...
Jeez...
Not having Iggy around is so inconvenient.
No matter what type of master you have,
a master is a master.
Without a master, an Entourage cannot go on living-
especially me, now that I have a heart.
So...
I can only kill-
kill the one who took my master from me.
That's right: "Kill."
If I kill the one who took her, she'll come back to me.
You'll come back, won't you, Re-l.
You're pretty good.
Really?
I'll ask you from now on.
Um... where are you going?
I'm worried about the ship.
I'll go take a look.
But outside, the winds...
If I kill the one who took her, she'll come back to me.
I'd think it should be able to fly in winds like these.
Re-l.
Iggy!
Why are you here?
I told you to return to Romdeau!
I told you, didn't I?
I said I'd never go anywhere without you.
You've... been infected with cogito...
Oh please, Re-l.
You're only noticing now?
Like I thought, you've got a few loose screws.
Or, was it that you weren't looking at me at all?
That hurts...
And I've always been with you too.
Since when?
In Romdeau...
when we were attacked by infected autoreivs.
But you must've passed the infection screening test.
I know how it works;
the test is meaningless.
You've known for that long?
But...
I haven't changed at all.
Iggy.
I've always obeyed only you
and always protected only you.
Right?
Am I wrong, Re-l?
And yet you don't need me...
The firewood...
Hey, Pino.
I'm reading a book!
Jeez.
Try being a little useful at least.
Open it!
So you've woken up, Re-l Mayer?
I've been dancing to your tune all this time, after all.
From now on, you'll dance to mine.
Who are you?
What are you saying?
I am your Entourage, Iggy.
I see.
If you're Iggy, then Iggy is already dead.
What?
Iggy would never talk like that.
Idiotic.
Speech patterns are just customizations!
That's not all.
To me... every single thing you say and do isn't Iggy.
If cogito caused these changes, it's as good as death!
Iggy was infected with cogito and died!
Shut up!
You're a selfish woman as usual, Re-l Mayer.
Don't kill me just because I've become inconvenient.
What about the Iggy who's stayed by
your side since you left Romdeau, then?
That's...
That's mean, Re-l.
Are you saying that isn't me?
Then what am I?
Tell me, Re-l.
I'm your favorite.
This speech setting was your choice too.
You...
My, my. You're ruining your cute face.
Girls shouldn't make scary faces like that.
Is that how you've been deceiving me?
Deceiving?
I can't accept an Entourage who deceives his master.
Is this an Entourage who has sworn loyalty?
Now that you've deceived me,
your master, you've ceased to be Iggy!
You're not Iggy!
Don't fuck with me, Re-l Mayer.
Just whose fault is all of this?
Selfish Re-l... useless Re-l... incomplete Re-l...
A woman like you... who else besides me could handle you?
What did you say?
You are far less competent than you think.
You passed yourself off as an exemplary
career-oriented Romdeau citizen without even knowing that?
Now, who do you have to thank for being able to do that?
Who always supported you when
you were impulsive and arrogant?
I did!
And you won't accept me?
That's my line!
I won't accept someone like you who doesn't need me!
What are you going to do with me?
Now you're starting to worry about yourself?
Answer me.
Nothing will change.
I'll just protect you.
Re-l, you said to me
that I, a heartless autoreiv, wouldn't understand your heart.
But I have a heart too.
Why wouldn't you notice?
We can't go back to Romdeau on this ship anymore,
but there's still that ship.
That was your idea, wasn't it.
What would stealing that ship accomplish?
Even if you go back to Romdeau as a cogito-infected autoreiv,
you'll only be disposed of.
Vince!
Pino...
See?
I'll help too.
Am I being good?
I'm happy, but try to find this kind.
Roger!
Vince, like this?
Yeah.
This too?
You're...
I won't hurt you.
Pino, let's go back...
You're...
Miss Re-l's...
Why do you have that gun?
Where is Miss Re-l?
Re-l will kill you someday.
Why do you need a woman like her?
You can't protect her.
You're fated to kill her, that's why.
I am?
I can see it.
I can see an ugly monster who
toys with a struggling, suffering Re-l.
And that monster is you, Vincent Law!
That's ridiculous!
Why would I kill Miss Re-l?
Those eyes...
Your eyes looked the same way when Re-l pointed the gun at you.
Those eyes will definitely kill Re-l...
My precious Re-l!
Where is Miss Re-l?
Re-l!
Iggy...
Good for you, Vincent.
I can't kill you now.
Miss Re-l...
I've lost.
Miss Re-l, I...
Re-...l...
Looks like we'll manage to fly.
Look, Re-l Mayer.
I ended up like this because of you.
A woman like you isn't even worth protecting.
But if you die, I'll lose my reason to live.
Why is someone like you my master?
Someone like you...!
Re-l...
Okay...?
What?
Don't hate me, okay?
Iggy...
It was hard for me...
but I wanted to be by your side, no matter what.
It's been hard for me for a long time, Re-l...
Because of a stupid woman like you!
Please, Re-l...
Don't hate me.
Yeah.
Don't worry, Iggy.
Re-l...
Re-l Mayer!
Don't worry...
I understand, you know...
that this kind of thing is sad.
Cogito...
No...
Did you become unhappy learning what grief is?
No, I probably became happy.
Why do you think that?
I don't know.
I'll put flowers on that girl's grave too!
Iggy...
After getting infected with cogito,
you could've chosen to leave me and become free.
And yet... why?
Miss Re-l...
What?
What do you want?
Um, well...
If you don't need anything, leave me alone.
Vincent!
Why?
Back there, you said you wouldn't shoot for now.
So, I'm returning it to you.
Let's go together, Miss Re-l.
Vincent...
U-Um, that was all I needed, so...
Iggy...
I still can't understand your heart.
But I'll understand your heart someday...
I'm sorry.
Please
could
you
stop
the
noise,
I'm
trying
to
get
some
rest
Please
could
you
stop
the
noise,
I'm
trying
to
get
some
rest
From
all
the
un
born
chic
head
From
all
the
un
born
chic
head
What's
that...?
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
What's
that...?
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
Mirror, mirror, on the wall...
A phrase from a familiar tale beckons us toward an illusory lake.
meditation  someone who looks like you
A face that resembles yours is reflected on the wavering surface.